<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Vision, Memory, and Language</title>
    <link>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Vision, Memory, and Language</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:20:10 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://britta-wstnr.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I have seen this before. Pattern completion in the human visual system and its role for memory</title>
      <link>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/posts/mariecurie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:20:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/posts/mariecurie/</guid>
      <description>From 2020 to 2022, I was funded by a Marie Curie Individual Fellowship of the EU Horizon 2020 scheme. This allowed me to join the lab of Prof. Floris de Lange at the Donders Institute at the Radboud University in Nijmegen to research visual anticipation and its relation to memory. Unfortunately, this fellowship was overshadowed by the COVID-19 pandemic, so progress on the project was a little slower than anticipated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi!
I am Britta Westner, a postdoctoral fellow at the Donders Institute, more precisely, at the Donders Centre for Cognition. Here, I am working in the lab of Assoc.-Prof. Vitória Piai.
My current research focuses mainly on the intersection of language and memory. Since my background is in visual neuroscience, I am naturally also interested in the intersection of language and vision. I work with electrophysiological data and have a focus on data analysis methods such as source reconstruction and MEG decoding.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Physical address:
Thomas van Aquinostraat 4
6525 GD NIJMEGEN
If you want to write me an email, you can do so via:
britta.westner [at] donders.ru.nl
My homepage entry at Radboud University is here:
https://www.ru.nl/personen/westner-b</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Publications</title>
      <link>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>You can find my full publication list on Google Scholar. I also have an ORCID.
Recent preprints Westner, BU, J Kujala, J Gross, and JM Schoffelen. 2023.
Towards a More Robust Non-Invasive Assessment of Functional Connectivity.
bioRxiv preprint. https://doi.org/10.1101/2023.02.06.527279.
Peer-reviewed papers Alves, JN, BU Westner, A Højlund, RS Weil, and SS Dalal. 2023.
Structural and Functional Changes in the Retina in Parkinson’s Disease.
Journal of Neurology, Neurosurgery &amp;amp; Psychiatry, jnnp-2022-329342. https://doi.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
