<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Vision, Memory, and Language</title>
    <link>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Vision, Memory, and Language</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 16:56:03 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://britta-wstnr.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New: Resources page</title>
      <link>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/posts/newresources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 16:56:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/posts/newresources/</guid>
      <description>There is a new content page on my website that links resources which I have created. At this point, it contains lectures and teaching material for MEG and EEG data analysis - but I will keep updating it whenever I create any new teaching material or tutorials.
If M/EEG data analysis is something you want to learn more about: go check it out here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I have seen this before. Pattern completion in the human visual system and its role for memory</title>
      <link>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/posts/mariecurie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:20:10 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/posts/mariecurie/</guid>
      <description>From 2020 to 2022, I was funded by a Marie Curie Individual Fellowship of the EU Horizon 2020 scheme. This allowed me to join the lab of Prof. Floris de Lange at the Donders Institute at the Radboud University in Nijmegen to research visual anticipation and its relation to memory. Unfortunately, this fellowship was overshadowed by the COVID-19 pandemic, so progress on the project was a little slower than anticipated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi!
I am Britta Westner, a postdoctoral fellow at the Donders Institute in The Netherlands, more precisely, at the Donders Centre for Cognition. Here, I am working in the lab of Assoc.-Prof. Vitória Piai.
My current research focuses mainly on the intersection of language and memory. Since my background is in visual neuroscience, I am naturally also interested in the intersection of language and vision. I work with electrophysiological data and have a focus on data analysis methods such as source reconstruction and MEG decoding.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Physical address:
Thomas van Aquinostraat 4
6525 GD NIJMEGEN
If you want to write me an email, you can do so via:
britta.westner [at] donders.ru.nl
My homepage entry at Radboud University is here:
https://www.ru.nl/personen/westner-b</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/resources/</guid>
      <description>On this page, I am collecting some resources that I created, mostly for data analysis of MEG and EEG data.
Source reconstruction of M/EEG data For the lab of Vitória Piai, I am creating a source reconstruction pipeline in FieldTrip. Not quite a tutorial, but with many explanatory comments in the text. Geared towards the data we handle in the lab, but I tried to make it clear if something is Donders-specific, so it might still be a good place to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Publications</title>
      <link>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://britta-wstnr.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>You can find my full publication list on Google Scholar. I also have an ORCID.
Recent preprints Westner, BU*, E Bosch*, C Utzerath, J Buitelaar, and FP de Lange. 2023.
Typical neural adaptation for familiar images in autistic adolescents.
bioRxiv preprint. https://doi.org/10.1101/2023.04.05.535670.
* These authors have contributed equally.
Westner, BU and JR King. 2023.
The best of two worlds: Decoding and source-reconstructing M/EEG oscillatory activity with a unique model.
bioRxiv preprint.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
